A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1934-1999
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Administrative Orders, 1940-1995, Extent: 11 cu. ft. (11 boxes). (Box 8-18)
  - A-252 1989 REGS. AD HOC PANEL, 1989 (Box 15)
  - A-252 FILE#1 PREHEARING REGS., 1989 (Box 15)
  - A-252 FILE #2 PREHEARING REGS., 1989 (Box 15)
  - A-252 POST HEARING REGS, 1989 (Box 16)
  - A-253 AD HOC ADVISORY PANEL REGS., 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-253 HEARING DAY REGS., 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-253 TRANSCRIPT PUBLIC HEARING, 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-253 TRANSCRIPT FROM PUBLIC MEETING AND HEARING REGS., 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-253 REGULATIONS, 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-253 REGS. PREHEARING (FILE NO. 1), 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-253 REGS. PREHEARING (FILE NO. 2), 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-253 REGS. PREHEARING (FILE NO. 3), 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-253 OPPOSITION LETTERS, 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-253 POST HEARING, 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - A-254 AD HOC ADVISORY COMMITTEE, 1991 (Box 16)
  - A-254 REGULATIONS, 1990 (Box 16)
  - A-254 REGULATIONS PREHEARING ORDER, 1991 (Box 17)
  - PREHEARING ORDER A-254 FILE NO. 2, 1991 (Box 17)
  - REQUEST FOR REGULATION CHANGES ORDER A-254, 1991 (Box 17)
  - A-254 PREHEARING REGS, EMERGENCY REGULATION VA. BEACH, 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - REGULATION ORDER A-254, 1991 (Box 17)
  - POST HEARING A-254, 1991 (Box 17)
  - A-254 AD. HOC. ADVISORY PANEL REGS., 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - REGULATIONS ORDER A-254 FILE NO. 1, 1991 (Box 17)
  - HEARING DAY ORDER A-254, 1991-1992 (Box 17)
  - PROPOSED REGULATION, 1992 (Box 17)
  - EMERGENCY ORDER A-255 (CREDIT & DEBIT CARDS), 1992 (Box 17)
  - POST HEARING ORDER A-256 FILE NO. 1, 1992 (Box 17)
  - PREHEARING A-256 FILE NO. 1, 1992 (Box 17)
  - REGULATION FILE (ORDER A-256) SUGGESTIONS FOR CHANGES IN REG., 1992 (Box 17)
  - POST HEARING A-256 HEARING TRANSCRIPT, 1992 (Box 17)
  - POST HEARING A-256 FILE NO. 1, 1992-1995 (Box 18)
  - ORDER A-261 PREHEARING AD HOC ADVISORY PANEL, 1992-1995 (Box 18)
  - ORDER A-261 PRE-NOIRA Regs., 1995 (Box 18)
  - ORDER A-261 REGULATIONS FILE NO. 1, 1994 (Box 18)
  - ORDER A-261 PREHEARING EXECUTIVE ORDER NO. 15 (REGULATIONS REVIEW), 1995 (Box 18)
  - ORDER A-261 PUBLIC MEETING, 1995 (Box 18)
- Series III: Legislation, 1952-1999, Extent: 4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box 19-22)
  - Legislation, 1952 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1954 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1956 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1958 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1962 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1964 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, By-laws, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1973 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, ABC Study Commission, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Legislation, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, 1980 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, Working papers, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, Package, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, General, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Legislation, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, Keg Registration, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, Original 5 Proposals, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, Proposed legislation, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, File #1, 1993 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, Legislative package, 1994 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, Legislative proposals, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, Legislative proposals, Rejects, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, General, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, 1996 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, 1998 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, Dead bills, 1999 (Box 21)
  - Legislation, 4-31(d1), nd (Box 22)
  - Legislation, Agency Legislation Proposals for the Session, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Legislation, 1960 (Box 22)
  - Legislation, Homosexuals, nd (Box 22)
  - Legislation, Procedures and reports, nd (Box 22)
  - Legislation, ABC Study Comm. Regs., Industry Recs., Etc., 1974 (Box 22)
  - Legislation, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Legislation, 7 Proposals, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Legislation, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Legislation, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Legislation, Discrimination legislation, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Legislation, Study Commission, nd (Box 22)
  - Legislation, Credit Card, Cash ABC Store Project, nd (Box 22)
- Series IV: Virginia Code and Regulations, 1968-1998, Extent: 15 cu. ft. (15 boxes). (Box 23-38 (no box 38))
  - ABC Intra-Dept. Communication, 1968-1977 (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-100 (Formerly 4-2) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-100 (Formerly 4-127) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-101 (Formerly 4-98.1) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-102 (Formerly 4-3) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-102 (Formerly 4-4) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-103 (Formerly 4-7) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-104 (Formerly 4-81) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-105 (Formerly 4-8) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-106 (Formerly 4.-2) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-107 (Formerly 4-20) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-108 (Formerly 4-10.1) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-109 (Formerly 4-10) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-110 (Formerly 4-17) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-111 (Formerly 4-98.51) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-111 (Formerly 4-11) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-111 (Formerly 3-36) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-111 (Formerly 4-98.41) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-112 (Formerly 4-144) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-114 (Formerly 4-98.7) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-115 (Formerly 4-13 & 4-14) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-115 (Formerly 4-21) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-115 (Formerly 4-13 & 4-14) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-116 (Formerly 4-22) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-116 (Formerly 4-23) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-117 (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-118 (Formerly 4-22.1) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-119 (Formerly 4-15 & 4-15.01) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-119 (Formerly 4-15.01) (Box 23)
  - Section 4.1-120 (Formerly 4-19) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-121 (Formerly 4-45) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-122 (Formerly 4-46) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-123 (Formerly 4-96.3) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-124 (Formerly 4-98.13 Generally) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-124 (Formerly 4-98.12 Election Results) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-125 (Formerly 4-98.12:1) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-126 (Formerly 4-98.12:2) (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-127 (Formerly 4-47) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-128 (Formerly 4-96) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-129 (Formerly 4-97 - Test Cases) (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-130 (Formerly 4-84.1) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-131 (Formerly 4-85) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-132 (Formerly 4-86) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-200 (Formerly 4-48) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-200 (Formerly 4-50) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-200 (Formerly 4-89) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-201 (Formerly 4-89) (Box 24)
  - Section 4.1-202 (Formerly 4-37.2) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-202 (Formerly 4-98.4) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-203 (Formerly 4-34) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-204 (Formerly 4-98.6) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-204 (Formerly 4-44) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-204 (Formerly 4-134) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-205 (Formerly 4-38) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-205 (Formerly 4-135) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-206 (Formerly 4-25) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-207 (Formerly 4-25) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-207 (Formerly 4-25.1(1)) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-207 (Formerly 4-29) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-208 (Formerly 4-25) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-209 (Formerly 4-25) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-210 (Formerly 4-98.2) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-210 (Formerly 4-98.3) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-211 (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-212 (Formerly 4-77) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-212 (Formerly 4-26) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-212 (Formerly 4-98.16) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-213 (Formerly 4-27) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-214 (Formerly 4-25) (Box 25)
  - Section 4.1-215 (Formerly 4-32) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-215 (Formerly 4-32.1) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-216 (Formerly 4-79.1) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-218 (Formerly 4-25) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-221 (Formerly 4-98.11 - Carriers) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-221 miscellaneous papers (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-222 (Formerly 4-31) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-223 (Formerly 4-98.9) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-223 (Formerly 4-31) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-223 (Formerly 4-98.17) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-224 (Formerly 4-31) (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-225 miscellaneous papers (Box 26)
  - Section 4.1-225 Miscellaneous Papers (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-225 (Formerly 4-37) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-226 (Formerly 4-31.1) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-227 (Formerly 4-37) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-228 (Formerly 4-37) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-228 Miscellaneous Papers (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-229 (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-230 (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-230 (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-230 (Formerly 4-30) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-230 (Formerly 4-33) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-231 (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-231 (Formerly 4-98.18) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-232 (Formerly 4-33) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-232 (Formerly 4-35) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-233 (Formerly 4-38) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-233 (Formerly 4-98.19) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-234 (Formerly 4-98.20) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-236 (Formerly 4-128 - 4-130) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-238 (Formerly 4.1-138) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-239 (Formerly 4.1-31, 4.1-32, 4-133) (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-240 Miscellaneous Papers (Box 27)
  - Section 4.1-300 (Formerly 4-57) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-301 (Formerly 4-57.1) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-302 (Formerly 4-58) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-303 (Formerly 4-71) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-304 (Formerly 4-62) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-304 Miscellaneous Papers (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-305 (Formerly 4-62) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-306 (Formerly 4-73) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-307 (Formerly 4-63) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-308 (Formerly 4-78) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-309 (Formerly 4-78.1) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-310 (Formerly 4-84) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-353 (Formerly 4-90.1) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-310 Miscellaneous Papers (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-311 (Formerly 4-72.1) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-312 (Formerly 4-74) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-313 (Formerly 4-75) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-314 (Formerly 4-77) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-315 (Formerly 4-61) (Box 28)
  - Section 4.1-316 (Formerly 4-61.1) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-317 (Formerly 4-81) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-318 (Formerly 4-83) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-319 (Formerly 4-70) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-320 (Formerly 4-69) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-321 (Formerly 4-93) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-322 (Formerly 4-52) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-323 (Formerly 4-87) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-324 (Formerly 4-60) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-325 (Formerly 4-98.10) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-325 Miscellaneous Papers (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-326 (Formerly 4-64) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-326 (Formerly 4-66) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-327 (Formerly 4-34.1) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-328 (Formerly 4-79.1) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-329 & 4.1-113 (Formerly 4-69.2) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-330 (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-331 (Formerly 4-65) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-333 (Formerly 4-51) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-334 (Formerly 4-52) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-335 (Formerly 4-82) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-336 (Formerly 4-53) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-337 (Formerly 4-54) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-338 (Formerly 4-55) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-339 THRU 4.1-348 (Formerly 4-56) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-343 (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-349 (Formerly 4-92) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-350 (Formerly 4-94) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-351 (Formerly 4-91) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-352 (Formerly 4-90) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-354 (Formerly 4-88) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-326 (Formerly 4-64) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-400 THRU 4.1-418 (Formerly 4-118.21 - 4.118.61 Wine Franchise Act) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-404 (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-500 THRU 4.1-517 (Formerly 4-118.21 - 4.118.20.1 Beer Franchise Act) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-500 (Formerly 4-118.4) (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-500 Miscellaneous Papers (Box 29)
  - Section 4.1-503 (Formerly 4-118.6) (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous papers (1998-2000 Sweepsteaks) (Box 30)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-10-10 THRU VAC 5-10-230 (Box 30)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-10-240 THRU VAC 5-10-350 (Box 30)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-10-360 THRU 3 VAC 5-10-400 (Box 30)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-10-410 THRU 3 VAC 5-10-470 (Box 30)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-10-480 (Box 30)
  - VR125-01-2 (Miscellaneous Papers) (Box 30)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-20 (Box 31)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-20 (Miscellaneous Papers) (Box 31)
  - VR125-01-2 (Miscellaneous Papers) (Box 31)
  - VR125-01-2 (Miscellaneous Papers) (Box 32)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-30 (Box 32)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-40 (Box 32)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-50 (Box 32)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-60 (Box 33)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-70 (Box 33)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-80 (Box 33)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-90 (Box 33)
  - VR125-01-2 (Miscellaneous Papers) (Box 34)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-20-100 (Box 34)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-30-10 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-30-20 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-30-30 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-30-40 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-30-50 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-30-60 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-30-70 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-40-10 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-40-20 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-40-30 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-40-40 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-40-50 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-10 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-20 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-30 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-40 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-50 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-60 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-70 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-80 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-90 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-100 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-120 (Box 35)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-130 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-140 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-150 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-160 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-170 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-180 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-190 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-200 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-210 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-220 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-50-110 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-60-10 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-60-20 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-60-30 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-60-40 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-60-50 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-60-60 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-60-70 (Box 36)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-60-80 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-60-90 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-10 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-20 (Box 37)
  - Gary Bond Letter (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-30 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-40 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-50 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-60 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-70 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-80 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-90 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-100 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-110 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-120 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-130 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-140 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-150 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-160 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-170 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-180 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-190 (Box 37)
  - Section 3 VAC 5-70-200 (Box 37)
  - Empty (Box 38)
- Series V: Special Interest Items, 1971-1996, Extent: 10 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 39-48)
  - APA-1985 Axselle's Proposal on Hearing Officers and Judicial Review (Preliminary Papers), 1986 (Box 39)
  - Cases Appealed to Court Precendential Value (Box 39)
  - Hearing Officer Manual (Box 39)
  - Goals and Objectives/Strategic Planning (Box 39)
  - Hearings - Cost (Box 39)
  - Alcoholism and Drug Abuse (Box 39)
  - Commission Loans State Treasury (Box 39)
  - Consent Settlement Policy and Procedure (Box 39)
  - Criminal Convictions (Procedures) (Box 40)
  - Decision on Issuance of Banquet Licenses Involving Colleges/Universities (Box 40)
  - Distribution of State Agency Reports, 1986 October (Box 40)
  - Elridge Maurice Atkinson t/a Jackies Place - Beer on and off Premises - VA Code Sec. 4-31(A)(2)(B)-so located peace and good order - 4-37(A)(3) and 4-34(D) (Box 40)
  - Importation, 1996 (Box 41)
  - Initial Decisions (Box 41)
  - KJ's Mini Mart, Inc. - KJ's Mini Mart - VA Code 4-31 (A)(2) Wine & Beer Off Premises Grocery store - Application School Objection (Box 41)
  - Cause Exists 4-31 (A)(2)(D); 4-31 (A)(2) Peace & Good Order, residences, school. 4-34 (D) and 4-37 A (3) Leonard Muse - T/A Green Valley Pharmacy - Wine & Beer Off Premises License VA. Code Sec 4-31 (A)(2)(B) Grocery store (Box 41)
  - License Management (Box 41)
  - Limousine Carriers (Box 41)
  - LOGO (A.B.C. Department) (Box 41)
  - The Lottery (Box 41)
  - Mailing Section (Misc.) (Box 41)
  - Malt Beverage Tax System, 1998 (Box 41)
  - Manual Defining - Elements of Offenses & Objections (Box 41)
  - Matthews, Lewis E. (Box 41)
  - M/B Referendum Info. (Box 41)
  - Media Coverage (Box 41)
  - Media Relations Policy (Media Coverage) (Box 41)
  - Media Task Force (Box 41)
  - Meeting with Industry / Sales to Underage Persons, 1990 June (Box 41)
  - Metric System (Box 41)
  - Minutes Submitted for Minute Book Entry (Box 41)
  - Mixed Beverage Localities (Box 41)
  - Moral Turpitude (Box 41)
  - Mystery Shopper Program Report (Box 41)
  - National Democratic Policy Committee (Box 41)
  - National Judicial College (Box 41)
  - New Office Building (Box 41)
  - NGA Federalism Task Force, 1987 December (Box 42)
  - Non Alcoholic Beverages (Box 42)
  - Notary Public File (Box 42)
  - O/C & Misc. Board Orders (Box 42)
  - Quarterly Reports and Board Actions Miscellaneous Folder (Box 42)
  - Rules of Practice (Box 42)
  - Rules of Practice 73-74 (Box 42)
  - Rules of Practice 66-71 (Box 42)
  - Rules of Practice 65 (Box 42)
  - Rules of Practice (Lahy - Shobe Committee Project) (Box 42)
  - Paper Flow, 1987 March (Box 43)
  - Penalties (Box 43)
  - Personnel Resolutions (Box 43)
  - Planning Districts (Box 43)
  - Public Authority Blanket Orders and Sample Orders (Box 43)
  - Police Authority Effective, 1971 May 4 (Box 43)
  - Police Authority Effective, A thru M, 1977 January (Box 43)
  - Police Authority Effective, N thru Z, 1977 January (Box 43)
  - Police Authority, E thru M (Box 43)
  - Police Authority, N thru Z (Box 43)
  - Possible Transition Hearings Div. (Box 43)
  - Private Labels (Box 43)
  - Privately Owned A.B.C. Stores (Box 43)
  - Procurement Planning, 1991-1992 FY (Box 43)
  - PSA's on Alcohol & Drugs (Box 43)
  - Publications (Box 44)
  - Quarterly Reports Permanent Records, 1960 March (Box 44)
  - Radio Communication (Box 44)
  - Rand McNally (Box 44)
  - Recodification of Title 4 (Box 44)
  - Regulation Pamphlet (Firms Looking into Printing Pamphlet) (Box 44)
  - Regulations Evaluations, 1987 (Box 44)
  - Regulations (Booklets) (Box 44)
  - Regulation Micro File (Box 44)
  - Risk Analysis Assessment (Box 45)
  - Old Quarterly Reports (4 Hanging Folders) (Box 45)
  - RNS (Box 45)
  - Roberts, Clarence W. (Box 45)
  - Rules of Changes, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Rules of Comments, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Rules of Practice Bowes Grocery (Box 45)
  - Rules of Practice Offers in Compromise (Box 46)
  - Rules of Practice (New), 1975 (Box 46)
  - SEA Club (Box 46)
  - Section 7.1-19 (Info - RNS) (Box 46)
  - Signature Stamp Authorization (Box 46)
  - John Smith Virginia Registrar (Box 46)
  - The Southland Copr. T/A 7-Eleven Store 1011-25923 VA Code Sec. 4-31 (A)(2)(B); Application - Wine & Beer Off Premises - 4-62 (1) & VR 125-01-5 (Box 46)
  - Of the Gstore - Sale to Minor Board Regulations Southland Corporation (Box 46)
  - Special Occupational Tax for Sale of Alcoholic Beverages (Box 46)
  - Specific Cases Heard by Board of Precendential Value (Box 46)
  - The Southland Corporation (7-Eleven Stores) (Box 46)
  - Bankruptcies (Box 46)
  - State Library (Microfilm) (Box 47)
  - Standards Committee (Box 47)
  - Sting Cases (Box 47)
  - Strategic Planning (Box 47)
  - Tax Agreement: A.B.C. & VA Dept. of Taxation (Interagency Agreement) (Box 47)
  - Tip Jar Games (Illegal Gambling) (Box 47)
  - (Tips) Intervention Procedures by Service of Alcohol, 1987 March 31 (Box 47)
  - Town Meeting (Box 47)
  - Cameras in Hearing Rooms (Box 47)
  - Under aged Persons (Box 48)
  - Vinters International Wine Franchise (Box 48)
  - VA Beer & Beverage Excise Tax Regulations (Box 48)
  - VA Beer Wholesalers Assoc. (Denny Gallager), 1988 March (Box 48)
  - The Virginia Register Act (Box 48)
  - Virginia Register Act (1) (Box 48)
  - Virginia Register Act (2) (Box 48)
  - Wage Differentials (Box 48)
  - Weekly Docket Sheets (Box 48)
  - Winn Dixie (Box 48)
  - Regulation Hearing Cassetts, 1992 October (Box 48)
  - Regulations Cassetts, 1990 (Box 48)